Guide to the Alfred A. Hart Photographs PC0002
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Prints, Series 1
  - Photograph album
    - Yuba Cascade and Hieroglyphic Rocks, on the Yuba River, near Crystal Lake., 100 (Box 1)
      G-165
    - Hieroglyphic Rocks, on the Yuba River, near Crystal Lake., 101 (Box 1)
      Hieroglyphic Rocks; Yuba River
      G-166
    - Hieroglyphic Rocks, on the Yuba River, near Crystal Lake., 102 (Box 1)
      Hieroglyphic Rocks
      G-151
      39
    - Hieroglyphic Rocks, on the Yuba River, near Crystal Lake., 103 (Box 1)
      G-152
    - Yuba River, above Cisco, Placer County., 104 (Box 1)
      G-173
      44
    - New Hampshire Rocks, on Yuba River. Summer view. 96 miles from Sacramento., 105 (Box 1)
      New Hampshire Rocks; Yuba River
      G-174
    - New Hampshire Falls, on Yuba River. Summer view. 96 miles from Sacramento., 106 (Box 1)
      New Hampshire Falls; Yuba River
      G-182
      47
    - New Hampshire Rocks, looking down the River., 107 (Box 1)
      New Hampshire Rocks; Yuba River; Flume
      G-183
    - Scene on Yuba River, above Cisco., 108 (Box 1)
      G-184
    - Summit Valley. Altitude 6,960 feet. Emigrant Mt. and R.R. Pass in dist., 109 (Box 1)
      Summit Valley; Emigrant Mountain
      G-192
      49
    - Castle Peak from Lava Bluff. 10,000 feet above the sea. Western Summit., 110 (Box 1)
      Castle Peak; Lava Bluff
      G-195
      50
    - Castle Peak and Yuba River, from Summit Valley. 102 miles from Sacramento., 111 (Box 1)
      Castle Peak; Yuba River; Wagons
      G-194
    - Scene near Donner Pass. Table Peak in the distance., 112 (Box 1)
      Donner Pass; Table Peak
      G-198
      51
    - Castle Peak from Grant’s Butte. Western Summit., 113 (Box 1)
      Castle Peak; Grant’s Butte
      G-216
      55
    - Scene at Lake Angela. Altitude 7,300 feet., 114 (Box 1)
      Lake Angela
      G-209
      53
    - Lake Angela. Mount King in the distance. Western Summit., 115 (Box 1)
      Lake Angela; Mount King
      G-210
      54
    - Camp near Summit Tunnel. Mount King in the distance., 116 (Box 1)
      Summit Tunnel; Mount King
      G-211
    - Bluffs in Donner Pass, Western Summit. 500 feet high. Altitude of Pass, 7,000 feet., 117 (Box 1)
      Donner Pass
      G-205
      52
    - Summit Tunnel--Eastern Portal. Length 1,660 feet, on the Western Summit., 118 (Box 1)
      Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06; Laborers
      G-212
    - Laborers and Rocks, near opening of Summit Tunnel., 119 (Box 1)
      Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06; Chinese; Laborers
      G-213
    - Scene near Summit Tunnel, Eastern slope of Western Summit., 120 (Box 1)
      Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06; Teamsters; Wagons; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon)
      G-214
    - Grant’s Peak and Palisade Rocks, from Western Summit., 121 (Box 1)
      Grant’s Peak; Palisade Rocks; Teamsters; Wagons
      G-215
    - Palisade Rocks, with Road and Teams descending Western Summit., 122 (Box 1)
      Palisade Rocks; Wagons; Teamsters
      G-218
      56
    - Lakeview Bluff, 350 feet high, from the Wagon Road., 123 (Box 1)
      Lakeview Bluff
      G-219
    - Road and Rocks at foot of Crested Peak, Eastern slope of Western Summit., 124 (Box 1)
      Crested Peak; Wagons; Teamsters; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon)
      G-220
    - Donner Lake from Summit. Lakeview Bluff on the right., 125 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Lakeview Bluff
      G-234
      Sierra Nevada Mountains, Donner Lake
      60
    - Donner Lake and Eastern Summit, from top of Summit Tunnel, western Summit., 126 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06
      G-235
    - Donner Lake, 110 miles from Sacramento. Eastern Summits 25 miles distant., 127 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake
      G-237
    - Boating Party on Donner Lake, between Eastern and Western Summits., 128 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Stanford, Jane Lathrop; Lathrop, Anna Maria
      G-242
      62
    - Donner Lake, with Crested Peak and Mt. Lincoln in distance., 129 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Crested Peak; Mt. Lincoln
      G-243
    - View on Donner Lake. Altitude 5,964 feet., 130 (Box 1)
      G-244
    - Donner Lake, with Pass in distance. Altitude above Lake, 1,126 feet., 131 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Donner Pass
      G-245
    - Donner Lake, Peak and Pass, from Wagon Road., 132 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Donner Peak; Donner Pass; Teamsters; Wagons
      G-246
      63
    - Stumps cut by Donner Party in 1846., 133 (Box 1)
      Donner Party; Hart, Alfred A. [?]
      G-193
    - Dry Creek Bridge, 17 miles from Sacramento., 134 (Box 1)
      Bridge; Locomotive; Boxcar
      G-8
      Valley of the Sacramento
      2
    - Locomotive on Trestle, near American River., 135 (Box 1)
      Trestle; Locomotive; American River; Conness
      G-6
    - Train and Curve, Jenny Lind Flat., 136 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Jenny Lind Flat
      G-16
      4
    - Bound for the Mountains., 137 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Smokestack of locomotive; Sacramento, California; telegraph pole
      G-7
    - Freight Depot at New Castle, Placer County. 31 miles from Sacramento., 138 (Box 1)
      Depot; Boxcar; Combine car; Newcastle, California
      G-22
      6
    - Locomotive on Turntable., 139 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Turntable
      G-20
      5
    - Rocklin Granite Quarry, 23 miles from Sacramento., 140 (Box 1)
      Rocklin Granite Quarry; Locomotive
      G-9
      3
    - Tangent below Pino, 22 miles from Sacramento., 141 (Box 1)
      Pino, California; Hart, Alfred A. (shadow and shadow of camera)
      G-17
    - Antelope Ridge, near New Castle, 30 miles from Sacramento., 142 (Box 1)
      Newcastle, California; Antelope Ridge
      G-19
    - Griffith’s, Granite Station., 143 (Box 1)
      Griffith’s Granite Station; Locomotive; Conness
      G-13
    - American River Bridge, 400 ft. long., 144 (Box 1)
      Bridge; Locomotive
      G-4
      1
    - Building Trestle at New Castle, Placer County., 145 (Box 1)
      G-21
    - Train on Embankment above Pino, with Hand-Car near., 146 (Box 1)
      Pino, California; Handcar
      G-18
    - Train at Griffith’s Station, Placer County., 147 (Box 1)
      Griffith’s Station; Placer County; Combine car
      G-12
    - View of the American River Bridge, near view., 148 (Box 1)
      American River Bridge; Locomotive
      G-5
    - Colfax, looking West, Illinoistown in distance., 149 (Box 1)
      Colfax, California; Illinoistown, California
      G-64
    - Colfax, looking East, Cape Horn 4 miles, and Giant’s Gap 20 miles distant., 150 (Box 1)
      Colfax, California
      G-65
    - Cape Horn, from Ravine below., 151 (Box 1)
      Cape Horn; Ravine
      G-72
    - Cape Horn, from American River. Railroad 1,400 feet above., 152 (Box 1)
      Cape Horn; American River
      G-73
    - Hog’s Back Cut, 60 feet deep. 2 miles above Alta., 153 (Box 1)
      Hog’s Back; Locomotive; Combine car
      G-109
    - American River, from Green Bluffs., 154 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; American River; Passengers
      G-113
    - View of the Forks of the American River, 3 miles above Alta, 155 (Box 1)
      American River; Locomotive; Passengers
      G-114
    - Prospect Hill Cut, 150 feet deep, 74 feet wide., 156 (Box 1)
      Prospect Hill; Locomotive; Combine car
      G-120
    - Railroad West from Fort Point, 76 miles., 157 (Box 1)
      G-123
    - Across Blue Canyon, looking East., 158 (Box 1)
      Blue Canyon; Combine car; Passengers
      G-130
    - Blue Canyon Embankment, 75 feet high., 159 (Box 1)
      Embankment; Blue Canyon
      G-131
      Sierra Nevada Mountains, Wesern Summit
    - Blue Canyon, 79 miles from Sacramento., 160 (Box 1)
      Blue Canyon; Locomotive; Combine car; Boxcar
      G-132
    - Across Blue Canyon, looking West., 161 (Box 1)
      Blue Canyon; Locomotive; Boxcar; Combine car
      G-133
    - Lost Camp Spur Cut, 80 miles from Sacramento., 162 (Box 1)
      Lost Camp Spur; Locomotive
      G-136
    - Frame for Snow Covering, interior view., 163 (Box 1)
      Snowshed
      G-138
    - Emigrant Gap. Snow Plow and Turntable., 164 (Box 1)
      Emigrant Gap, California; snowplow; Turntable
      G-139
      36
    - Emigrant Gap, West from Tunnel., 165 (Box 1)
      Emigrant Gap, California; Locomotive; Combine car
      G-143
      37
    - Emigrant Gap Tunnel, Wall and Snow Covering., 166 (Box 1)
      Emigrant Gap Tunnel; Snowshed
      G-144
    - Emigrant Gap, looking East, Yuba Mountains in distance., 167 (Box 1)
      Emigrant Gap, California; Locomotive; Flatcar; Yuba Mountains; telegraph pole; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon)
      G-145
    - Bear Valley, 85 miles from Sacramento., 168 (Box 1)
      Bear Valley; Locomotive; Combine car; telegraph pole
      G-142
    - Valley North Fork of Yuba, above Emigrant Gap. Old Man Mountain., 169 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Old Man Mountain
      G-146
    - Cement Ridge, Old Man Mountain in distance., 170 (Box 1)
      Cement Ridge; Old Man Mountain; Locomotive; Boxcar
      G-147
      38
    - Miller’s Bluffs, near Crystal Lake. Old Man Mountain in distance., 171 (Box 1)
      Miller’s Bluffs; Old Man Mountain
      G-148
    - Echo Point, opposite Crystal Lake, looking West., 172 (Box 1)
      Echo Point; telegraph pole
      G-149
    - Echo Point and Rattlesnake Mountain, near Crystal Lake., 173 (Box 1)
      Echo Point; Rattlesnake Mountain; telegraph pole
      G-150
    - Railroad, below Cisco and Crystal Lake., 174 (Box 1)
      Trestle; Crystal Lake; Cisco, California
      G-153
    - Foot of Black Butte, above Crystal Lake., 175 (Box 1)
      Black Butte; Crystal Lake
      G-154
    - Black Butte, 91 miles from Sacramento., 176 (Box 1)
      G-155
      40
    - Crystal Lake and Railroad, from Black Butte., 177 (Box 1)
      Crystal Lake; Black Butte
      G-156
    - South Yuba Valley and Summit, from Black Butte., 178 (Box 1)
      Yuba Valley; Black Butte
      G-157
    - Old Man Mountain. near Meadow Lake. Altitude 7,500., 179 (Box 1)
      Old Man Mountain; Meadow Lake; camera and photographer
      G-172
    - Meadow Lake, 6,800 elevation. Knickerbocker Hill and Old Man Mountain., 180 (Box 1)
      Meadow Lake; Knickerbocker Hill; Old Man Mountain
      G-171
    - North Fork of South Yuba, near Meadow Lake., 181 (Box 1)
      G-170
    - Oneonta, at Cisco., 182 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California; Locomotive; Oneonta
      G-179
      46
    - Main Street, Upper Cisco, 5,911 feet elevation., 183 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California; Teamsters; Wagons
      G-176
      45
    - Upper Cisco, Rattlesnake and Yuba Mountains., 184 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California; Rattlesnake Mountain; Yuba Mountain; Valley
      G-177
    - Depot at Cisco, Altitude 5,900 feet., 185 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California; Depot; Boxcar; Locomotive; Idaho; telegraph pole
      G-178
    - View of the South Yuba, below Cisco., 186 (Box 1)
      South Yuba River; Cisco, California
      G-158
    - Summits of Sierras. 8,000 to 10,000 feet altitude., 187 (Box 1)
      G-207
    - Castle Peak, a Western Summit, 10,000 feet altitude., 188 (Box 1)
      Castle Peak
      G-196
    - Summit of Castle Peak, 10,000 feet altitude., 189 (Box 1)
      G-197
    - Summit of Castle Peak, from the North-west., 190 (Box 1)
      G-200
    - Summit Valley, from Emigrant Mount. Alt. 8,200 ft., looking toward Cisco., 191 (Box 1)
      Summit Valley; Emigrant Mountain; Cisco, California
      G-201
    - Anderson Valley and Devil’s Peak, from Emigrant Mountain, Western Summit., 192 (Box 1)
      Anderson Valley; Devil’s Peak; Emigrant Mountain
      G-202
    - Summit Station, Western Summit., 193 (Box 1)
      Summit Station; Snowshed
      G-224
      57
    - Lakes in Anderson Valley, from Lava Bluff., 194 (Box 1)
      Anderson Valley; Lake; Lava Bluff
      G-199
    - American Peak, in Spring, View near the Pass, Western Summit., 195 (Box 1)
      American Peak; Lake
      G-203
    - Shaft House over Summit Tunnel, American Peak in distance., 196 (Box 1)
      Shaft House; Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06; American Peak
      G-204
    - Summit Tunnel, before completion--Western Summit--Altitude 7,042 feet., 197 (Box 1)
      Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 06
      G-223
    - East Portal of Summit Tunnel, Western Summit. Length 1,660 feet., 198 (Box 1)
      G-222
    - East Portal of Summit Tunnel, and Wagon Road from Tunnel No. 7., 199 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 06; Summit Tunnel; Teamsters; Wagons
      G-221
    - Bluff and Snow Bank in Donner Pass, Western Summit. Altitude 1,092 feet., 200 (Box 1)
      Donner Pass; Snowbank; Wagons
      G-206
    - Melting of a Snow Bank. Scene on the Summits in August., 201 (Box 1)
      Snowbank
      G-208
    - East Portals of Tunnels No. 6 and 7, from Tunnel No. 8., 202 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 06; Summit Tunnel; Tunnel No. 07; Tunnel No. 08; Black Point
      G-230
      59
    - Donner Lake, Tunnels No. 7 and 8 from Summit Tunnel, Eastern Summit in distance., 203 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Tunnel No. 07; Tunnel No. 08; Summit Tunnel; Black Point; Passengers; Excursion party
      G-236
    - Heading of East Portal. Tunnel No. 8, from Donner Lake Railroad, Western Summit., 204 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 08; Chinese; Black Point
      G-231
    - Railroad on Pollard’s Hill, 1,100 feet above Donner Lake., 205 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Pollard’s Hill
      G-248
    - Coldstream Valley, from Tunnel No. 13., 206 (Box 1)
      Coldstream Valley; Tunnel No. 13
      G-239
      61
    - Coldstream, Eastern slope of Western Summit., 207 (Box 1)
      Coldstream, California; River; Chinese
      G-241
    - View from Crested Peak, 8,500 ft. alt. Donner Lake 1,500 ft. below. R.R. 1,000 ft. below., 209 (Box 1)
      Crested Peak; Donner Lake
      G-229
      58
    - Loaded Teams, from Cisco., 210 (Box 1)
      Teamsters; Wagons
      G-167
    - West Portal Tunnel No. 1, Grizzly Hill., 211 (Box 1)
      Grizzly Hill Tunnel; Tunnel No. 01; Locomotive; Combine car; Boxcar
      G-129
    - North Fork of Yuba River, between Cisco and Meadow Lake., 212 (Box 1)
      Yuba River; Laborers
      G-169
    - Snow Covering, below Cisco., 213 (Box 1)
      G-175
    - Emigrant Gap Ridge. 84 miles. Old Man Mountain, Red Mountain, Castle Peak in dist., 214 (Box 1)
      Emigrant Gap, California; Old Man Mountain; Red Mountain; Castle Peak
      G-140
    - Bear Valley and Yuba Canyon, from Emigrant Gap., 215 (Box 1)
      Bear Valley; Yuba Canyon
      G-141
    - View at Shady Run, 73 miles from Sacramento., 216 (Box 1)
      Shady Run
      G-121
    - All Aboard for Virginia City. Wells, Fargo & Co.’s Express., 217 (Box 1)
      Cisco, California; Wells, Fargo; Teamsters; Wagons; Stagecoach; Locomotive; Depot
      G-180
    - Tunnel No. 3, above Cisco., 218 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 03
      G-190
    - Scene on the Truckee River, near Donner Lake., 220 (Box 1)
      Truckee River
      G-258
      Sierra Nevada Mountains, Truckee River. Eastern Summit
      66
    - Truckee River, below Truckee Station, looking West, toward Donner Lake., 221 (Box 1)
      G-259
      67
    - Truckee River, below Truckee Station, looking toward Eastern Summit., 222 (Box 1)
      G-260
    - Truckee River, approaching the Eastern Summits., 223 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Locomotive; Flatcar
      G-261
    - First Crossing of the Truckee River, 133 miles from Sacramento., 224 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Bridge; Boy
      G-263
      68
    - Bridge over First Crossing Truckee River, 204 feet long., 225 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Bridge
      G-264
    - Interior of Bridge over First Crossing of the Truckee River., 226 (Box 1)
      Bridge; Truckee River
      G-265
    - Profile Rock, near the First Crossing of the Truckee River., 227 (Box 1)
      Profile Rock
      G-262
    - Truckee River entering the Eastern Summits. Tunnel No. 14 134 miles., 228 (Box 1)
      G-267
      69
    - American River Bridge. Railroad around Cape Horn, 1,400 feet above., 229 (Box 1)
      American River Bridge
      G-79
    - View on the American River, below Cape Horn., 230 (Box 1)
      American River
      G-80
    - Bloomer Cut, near Auburn, 800 feet long and 63 feet high., 231 (Box 1)
      Bloomer Cut; Locomotive; Flatcar
      G-37
    - Capitol Granite Quarry at Rocklin, 22 miles from Sacramento., 232 (Box 1)
      Capitol Granite Quarry; Rocklin; Laborers
      G-10
    - Cutting granite at Rocklin., 233 (Box 1)
      Granite quarry; Laborers; Rocklin
      G-11
    - Railroad wharves, at Sacramento City., 234 (Box 1)
      Sacramento, California; Flatcar; Ships’ masts; Wharves
      G-1
    - J Street, Sacramento City, from the Levee., 235 (Box 1)
      Sacramento, California; Brannan House; Locomotive; A.A. Sargent
      G-3
    - Cathedral Rocks, Truckee River., 236 (Box 1)
      Cathedral Rocks; Bridge; Truckee River
      G-266
    - Crested Peak, from Grant’s Butte, 237 (Box 1)
      Crested Peak; Grant’s Butte
      G-217
    - Snow Plow, at Cisco., 239 (Box 1)
      Snowplow
      G-181
    - Engine House and Train, Rocklin, 22 miles from Sacramento., 240 (Box 1)
      Boxcar; Rocklin, California; Engine House
      G-14
    - Engine House and Turntable, Rocklin, 22 miles from Sacramento., 241 (Box 1)
      Turntable; Rocklin, California
      G-15
    - West of Clipper Gap, Placer County., 242 (Box 1)
      G-55
    - Clipper Gap, 43 miles from Sacramento., 243 (Box 1)
      G-56
    - Cut near New England Mills, 49 miles from Sacramento., 244 (Box 1)
      New England Mills
      G-58
    - Railroad around Cape Horn, from the Canyon., 245 (Box 1)
      Cape Horn; Canyon
      G-74
    - Constructing Snow Cover. Scene near the Summit., 246 (Box 1)
      Snowshed; Laborers
      G-225
    - Frame of Snow Covering, 90 miles from Sacramento., 247 (Box 1)
      G-189
      48
    - Lower Cascade, near Long Side Track., 248 (Box 1)
      Yuba River; Long Side Track; Waterfall
      G-185
    - Lower Cascade Bridge, above Cisco., 249 (Box 1)
      Bridge
      G-186
    - Upper Cascade, 98 miles from Sacramento., 250 (Box 1)
      Yuba River; Waterfall
      G-187
    - Upper Cascade Bridge, above Cisco., 251 (Box 1)
      G-188
    - Snow Gallery around Crested Peak. Timbers 12x14 in., 20 in. apart., 252 (Box 1)
      Snowshed; Crested Peak; Hart, Alfred A. [?]
      G-232
    - Inside view of Snow Gallery at Summit. Bolting the Frame to the Rocks., 254 (Box 1)
      G-233
    - From Tunnel No. 10 looking West. Building Wall across the Ravine., 255 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 10; Cement Ridge; Laborers
      G-226
    - Crested Peak and Tunnel No. 10. Eastern slope of Western Summit., 256 (Box 1)
      Crested Peak; Tunnel No. 10; Cement Ridge
      G-227
    - Tunnel No. 12, Strong’s Canyon., 257 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 12; Strong’s Canyon; Tunnel Spur
      G-228
    - Castle Peak, from Railroad, above Donner Lake., 258 (Box 1)
      G-238
    - Coldstream Valley, East of Donner Lake., 259 (Box 1)
      Coldstream Valley
      G-240
    - Mist rising from Donner Lake. Early morning view., 260 (Box 1)
      G-249
    - Railroad around Crested Peak. View from foot of Donner Lake., 261 (Box 1)
      Donner Lake; Crested Peak
      G-247
    - Depot at Truckee, 119 miles from Sacramento., 262 (Box 1)
      Depot; Locomotive; Truckee, California
      G-255
    - Scene at Truckee, Nevada County., 263 (Box 1)
      Truckee, California; Lumberyard; Webber House
      G-256
    - Truckee River, at Truckee Station, 15 miles from Lake Tahoe., 264 (Box 1)
      G-257
    - Boca. Crossing of Little Truckee., 265 (Box 1)
      Boca; Little Truckee River; Locomotive; Flatcar; Bridge
      G-268
    - View of Truckee River, near Camp 24., 266 (Box 1)
      G-269
    - View near State Line, Truckee River., 267 (Box 1)
      State Line; Truckee River; telegraph pole
      G-273
      70
    - Boundary Peak and Tunnel No. 15, 137 miles from Sacramento., 268 (Box 1)
      Boundary Peak; Tunnel No. 15; Locomotive; Combine car; Boxcar
      G-270
    - Tunnel No. 15, looking East, toward Nevada., 269 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 15; Truckee River; telegraph pole
      G-271
    - Tunnel No. 15, near Camp 24., 270 (Box 1)
      Tunnel No. 15; telegraph pole
      G-272
    - No title., 271 (Box 1)
      G-275
      72
    - No title., 272 (Box 1)
      G-276
    - Bridge at Eagle Gap, Truckee River., 273 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Bridge; Eagle Gap
      G-277
    - Bridge over Truckee River, Eagle Gap., 274 (Box 1)
      Bridge; Eagle Gap; Truckee River
      G-278
    - Eagle Gap, Truckee River., 275 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Eagle Gap; telegraph pole
      G-279
      73
    - Eagle Gap, Truckee River., 275 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Eagle Gap
      G-274
      71
    - View near Verdi, Truckee River., 276 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Verdi
      G-280
    - Looking toward Verdi, Truckee River, 140 miles from Sacramento., 277 (Box 1)
      G-281
    - Bridge below Verdi, Truckee River., 278 (Box 1)
      Bridge; Truckee River; Verdi
      G-282
    - Fourth Crossing of the Truckee River. 147 miles from Sacramento., 279 (Box 1)
      G-283
      74
    - Granite Quarry, near Reno., 280 (Box 1)
      Granite quarry; Flatcar
      G-284
    - Reno and Washoe Range in Distance. From base of Sierra Nevada Mountains., 281 (Box 1)
      Reno, Nevada; Washoe Range; Desert
      G-285
    - Piute Squaws and Children. At Reno., 282 (Box 1)
      Piute Indians; Reno, Nevada
      G-287
      Washoe Range, Truckee River
      75
    - Piute Indians. At Reno., 283 (Box 1)
      Indians; Reno, Nevada
      G-288
    - Freight Depots at Reno, 154 miles from Sacramento., 284 (Box 1)
      Reno, Nevada; Depot; Teamsters; Wagons
      G-289
    - Scene at Depot, at Reno., 285 (Box 1)
      Reno, Nevada; Indians; Depot
      G-290
    - Virginia Street, from the Bridge, Reno., 286 (Box 1)
      Reno, Nevada; Wagons; Virginia Street; Pioneer Brewery; Milatovich Groceries & Liquors
      G-291
      76
    - Entering Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 287 (Box 1)
      Locomotive; Flatcar; telegraph pole
      G-292
    - Looking across Truckee Meadows, toward Sierra Nevada Mountains, near Camp 37., 288 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Truckee Meadows
      G-293
    - Truckee Meadows. Sierra Nevada Mountains 20 miles distant., 289 (Box 1)
      Truckee Meadows; Desert; Train; Boxcar; Locomotive; telegraph pole
      G-294
    - Truckee Meadows, from Camp 37, 162 miles from Sacramento., 290 (Box 1)
      Train; Truckee Meadows; Desert; Flatcar; Boxcar; Locomotive
      G-295
      77
    - Scene Near Camp 37, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 291 (Box 1)
      Train; Desert; telegraph pole
      G-296
    - Below Camp 37, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 292 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; telegraph pole
      G-297
    - Crossing of Wagon Road, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 293 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Wagon Road; telegraph pole
      G-298
    - Cottonwood Valley, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 294 (Box 1)
      Cottonwood Valley; Truckee River; telegraph pole
      G-299
      78
    - Scene on Bank of Truckee River, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 295 (Box 1)
      G-300
    - Basaltic Rocks, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 296 (Box 1)
      Basaltic Rocks
      G-301
    - View from Basaltic Rocks, looking East., 297 (Box 1)
      G-302
    - Limestone Point, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 298 (Box 1)
      Limestone Point; Canyon; telegraph pole
      G-303
      79
    - Truckee River and Railroad at Lime Point. Sierra Nevada Mountains 35 miles distant., 299 (Box 1)
      Truckee River; Lime Point; Canyon; telegraph pole
      G-304
    - Pleasant Valley, Lower Canyon of Truckee., 300 (Box 1)
      Pleasant Valley; Truckee River; Canyon; Hart, Alfred A. (photographer’s wagon); telegraph pole
      G-305
    - Pleasant Valley, looking West, Lower Canyon of Truckee River., 301 (Box 1)